http://www.cinemawest.com/page/12384/privacy-policy

Gifts & Rewards
Current Theater:
ANGELS THEATRE
Privacy Policy
Cinema West Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to Cinema West. We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. This information helps us improve your movie going experience with better content, services and opportunities. This policy tells you about the information gathering and dissemination that we conduct. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically for updates.
The Information We Collect
We ask our users to register when providing us information through the Cinema West site and services (collectively, the "Service"). Through our online registration process, we collect a variety of information about the user, which may include, among other things, name of the person registering, location, gender, phone number, email address, Login ID, Member Name and password. Cinema West may also request and collect other information from time to time.
We automatically track information related to use of the Service. This information may include, among other things, URL tracking information, what browser the user is using, the user's IP address, pages and ads viewed by a user and selections or other actions taken on the Service. We may track usage through cookies. A cookie is a small data file written to a user's hard drive. Cookies may be used to, among other things, allow automated log-in and may contain information such as a Login ID or other information about preferences or Internet use.
We also collect information about your movie preferences. For example, we may collect, among other things, information such as what movies you purchase tickets to or what theaters you attend. We may save information sent or posted to the Service. For example, we may save messages posted in our chat rooms or other message areas or feedback left for other users. We may collect correspondence, such as emails or letters, sent to us. We may collect user responses to online polls, ads, surveys, electronic newsletters and questionnaires. We may collect information provided in employment applications.
Deletion of Information and Records
While Cinema West may track and store information, Cinema West shall not be obligated to do so and may delete any information and records, in whole or in part, at any time.
What we use the information for
We use the demographic information to enhance your user experience by, among other things, delivering you content that is relevant to your interests. We may use the contact information you provide us to notify you of new services or special deals that we or our partners are offering, to distribute movie related information to you or to conduct surveys or other similar activities. When you register with us, you may choose to opt-out of receiving these notices or mailings from Cinema West, Inc; to do so, simply uncheck the "I want to receive discounts, contest information and special promotions from Cinema West via email" box on the registration page.
Cinema West does not sell or rent personal information about its customers to any third parties at this time. Cinema West does, however, perform statistical analyses of customer usage in order to measure interest in, and use of, the various parts of the Company's Web site, and the Company may share that information with current and prospective advertisers, and other interested third parties. This information is aggregated data only (such as statistics), and contains no personally identifiable information whatsoever.
Please note that Cinema West may share your contact, demographic and other personally identifiable information with our theater partners. Our theater partners may share your information with third parties, which may result in, among other things, unsolicited inquiries, messages, or offers from third parties. The maintenance and/or use of such information by our partners is out of the control of Cinema West. If you do not wish to be contacted by our theater partners, simply uncheck the "I want to receive discounts, contest information and special promotions from Cinema West, via email" box on the registration page.
Please note that Cinema West may sell, share or transfer personally identifiable information about its customers with any successor in interest (e.g. if the Company is sold to a third party). Additionally, in certain cases, Cinema West may be required to disclose your personally identifiable information when the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case or administrative investigation.
Cinema West users should also be aware that if they voluntarily disclose personal information in any chat areas or bulletin boards within Cinema West's Web site, that information might be collected and disseminated by third-parties, and result in, among other things, unsolicited inquiries, messages, and offers from third parties. This third-party conduct is out of the control of the Company.
Security
Cinema West has implemented security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We protect the secure areas of our Site with a firewall.
Choice/Opt-Out
Cinema West allows users the option to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at registration. If you decide later to opt-out you can contact us by sending e-mail to support@cinemawest.com.
Employment Applications
Employment Applications submitted through Cinema West's Web Site are stored by Cinema West for a specified period of time and the information contained in the applications is not released to any person that is not an employee of the Cinema West group of movie theaters, except as required by law. We will only contact an applicant to discuss employment interest and for no other purpose.
Questions
If you have any questions about the Cinema West Service or this privacy statement, you can email us at info@cinemawest.com or write us at:
Cinema West, P.O. Box 750595
Petaluma CA 94975
Terms of Use
Welcome to Cinema West. The following are the rules or "Terms" that govern use of the Cinema West web sites and the Services offered on the Site such as email, chat, searches, links, etc. (collectively, "Site"). By using the Site, you agree to be bound by these Terms and to follow these Terms and all applicable laws and regulations governing the Site. Cinema West reserves the right to change these Terms at any time, effective immediately upon posting on the Site.
Permitted Use
You are only authorized to view and to retain a copy of pages of this Site for your own personal use. Any reproduction, publication, or further distribution or public exhibition of materials provided at this site in whole or in part is strictly prohibited. The content and software on this Site is the property of Cinema West and/or its suppliers and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. We post a legal notice and various credits on pages of the Site. Please do not remove this notice or these credits, or any additional information contained along with the notices and credits.
Links and Search Results
The Site may automatically produce search results that reference or links to third party sites throughout the World Wide Web. Cinema West has no control over these Sites or the Content within them. Cinema West cannot guarantee, represent or warrant that the Content contained in the Sites is accurate, legal and/or inoffensive. Cinema West does not endorse the Content of any third party Site, nor do can we warrant that they will not contain viruses or otherwise impact your computer. By using the Site to search for or link to another site, you agree and understand that you may not make any claim against Cinema West for any damages or losses, whatsoever, resulting from your use of the Site to obtain search results and/or to link to another site. However, if you have a problem with a link from the Site, please let us know at customerservice@cinemawest.com, and we will investigate the link and take appropriate action.
Privacy
We believe that your privacy and the privacy of all our users is important. Please review our privacy policies. If you post any original Content to the Site, by electronic mail or otherwise, we will treat it as non-confidential and non-proprietary to you. By posting it to the Site, you authorize us to use or allow others to distribute, reproduce or otherwise use the Content. Cinema West is not liable for any lost data resulting from the operation of our Site and/or the enforcement of the Terms. We urge all users to maintain their own back up versions of any content they submit to the Site.
U.S. Export controls. Software from this site is further subject to United States export controls. No software from this site may be downloaded or otherwise exported or reexported (i) into (or to a national or resident of) Cuba, Iraq, Libya, North Korea, Iran, Syria, or any other country to which the U.S. has embargoed goods; or (ii) to anyone on the U.S. Treasury Department's list of Specially Designated Nationals or the U.S. Commerce Department's Table of Deny Orders. By downloading or using the Software, you represent and warrant that you are not located in, under the control of, or a national or resident of any such country or on any such list.
DISCLAIMER
Cinema West does not promise that the Site or any services, such as email, links or searches offered on the Site will be error-free, uninterrupted, nor that it will provide specific results from use of the Site or any Content, search or link on it. The Site, and its Content are delivered on an "as-is" and "as-available" basis. Cinema West can not ensure that files you download from the Site will be free of viruses or contamination or destructive features. Cinema West disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including also any implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. Cinema West will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the use of this Site, including without limitation, direct, indirect, incidental, punitive and consequential damages.
Disputes
If there is any dispute about or involving the Site, by using the Site, you agree that the dispute will be governed by the laws or the State of California without regard to its conflict of law provisions. You agree to personal jurisdiction by and venue in the State of California, County of Sonoma and federal courts of the Northern District of the State of California.
Indemnity
You agree to indemnify and hold Cinema West, its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents and other partners and employees, harmless from any loss, liability, claim or demand, including reasonable attorney's fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of your use of the Site, including also your use of the Site to provide a link to another Site or to upload content or other information to the Site.
ALWAYS BE IN THE KNOW
Subscribe to ANGELS THEATRE email newsletter to receive updates and event notifications. You don't have to worry, we'll respect your inbox.
©2020 Website by The Boxoffice CompanyOpens in new window for Cinema West
Choose your theatre
Search for Theater
ANGELS THEATRE
1228 South Main Street,
Angels Camp, CA 95222
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
BOULEVARD 14 CINEMA
200 C Street,
Petaluma, CA 94952
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
CIVIC PLAZA 12 CINEMA
9711 Ninth Avenue,
Hesperia, CA 92345
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
CONTRA COSTA STADIUM CINEMA
555 Center Avenue,
Martinez, CA 94553
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
COUNTRY CLUB CINEMA
2405 Butano Drive,
Sacramento, CA 95825
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
FAIRFAX THEATRE
9 Broadway,
Fairfax, CA 94930
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
FORTUNA THEATRE
1241 Main Street,
Fortuna, CA 95540
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
LIVERMORE 13 CINEMA
2490 First Street,
Livermore, CA 94550
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
MAGIC VALLEY CINEMA 13
1485 Pole Line Road East,
Twin Falls, ID 83301
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
PALLADIO 16 CINEMA
240 Palladio Parkway,
Folsom, CA 95630
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
PALLADIO LUXE CINEMA
400 Palladio Parkway,
Folsom, CA 95630
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
RHEEM THEATRE
350 Park Street,
Moraga, CA 94556
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
STATE THEATRE & MULTIPLEX
322 Main Street,
Woodland, CA 95695
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
VERANDA LUXE CINEMA & IMAX
2035 Diamond Boulevard,
Concord, CA 94520
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
VILLAGE CINEMA
3711 East Longwing Lane - The Village at Meridian,
Meridian, ID 83646
Add to favorites
Choose theatre
